biowebspin.com 2013-12-13

# Privacy Policy - Biowebspin | Biowebspin

Biowebspin pays a lot of attention to the security and good use of its members data.

The treatment of personal and professional data on Biowebspin is the subject of a declaration to the Commission Nationale Informatique et Liberté (CNIL), declaration n° 1592981.

**_1.Information We Collect and How we Use them_**

The information that we collect, store and use is exclusively intended to help you build your professional network. When registering or using any of our services you expressly consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your profile information as described in this Privacy Policy.

More specifically, we collect information:

-when you register an account to become a Biowebspin member.

-when you view and Biowebspin with Biowebspin community, pages, features, and functionality of Biowebspin or of third party applications and you provide any additional information (groups, files, topics, descriptions…). Providing additional information about yourself beyond what is minimally required at registration is entirely up to you. Any information you provide at registration or in the Profile section may be used by Biowebspin as described in the Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy, including for the purpose of allowing professional opportunities to find you on Biowebspin, or for serving more relevant advertisements on Biowebspin.  If you submit information for the propose of publishing on Biowebspin (such as a company or an organization's profile, an event, a document…), you agree that any of this information can be made publicly available to any Biowebspin members or visitors as well as partners of Biowebspin.

-through cookies (files placed on your computer) and other technologies that allow us to recognize you, customize your experience, and serve advertisements both on and off Biowebspin. Our site and third parties such as advertisers may add a cookie to help analyze web traffic or to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. We use Google analytics to get information on Biowebspin website traffic and Google adsence as an intermediate Advertiser  To opt out of Google’s use of cookies, please visit the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). To know more about the use of Google Analytics and Google Adsense, we advise you to read their Terms and Conditions.

-when you ask for email notifications or promotional communications. You can control your messaging preferences. Emails however which are based on a specific action of the user (such as account passwords, invoices…  etc.) are sent automatically and cannot be turned off. By using any of our services you agree that these automatically generated emails will be sent to you.

-when you interact with third party services available through Biowebspin

-when you interact with Biowebspin’s customer service (contact form) in order to accurately categorize and respond to customer inquiries and investigate breaches of our terms.

 We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent except where it is necessary to carry out your instructions (to process your payment information, for example).

_2.[ **Your Information Choices and Rights**](http://www.linkedin.com/static?key=privacy_policy#pri-3)_

You can:

-review, enhance or edit your personal information through your personal profile page and your company or organization if you are the owner and have been given the right to manage your company or organization profile

-control the messages you receive from Biowebspin and other members

-close or tell us to close your Biowebspin account or your company or organization if you are the owner and have been given the right to manage your company or organization profile.

To simplify and not confuse the member, all the information which are posted by the member are public on Biowebspin and on the web (except the private message).

Pursuant to the amended French data protection law No. 78-17 of 6 January 1978, and on condition that you provide proof of your identity, you may access, amend, correct and delete data relating to you and oppose their use at no cost to You. This opposition is possible at any time by going directly to your account on Biowebspin ’s website [www.biowebspin.com](http://www.biowebspin.com/) or by sending email to Biowebspin by the contact form or by sending a letter by post to the address below: Biowebspin 123 bis chemin des pannetières 69126 Brindas France.

**_3.Your obligations and your responsibility_**

-Do not abuse the Biowebspin service by using it to spam, abuse, harass, or otherwise violate the Terms and Conditions or Privacy Policy.

-Members may make certain information or contents (including but not limited to biographical data, photos and videos) available on the website. Members are wholly responsible for all such information and contents, including information that reveals race, ethnic origin, sexual orientation, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership or that concerns an individual’s health. By providing such information on the website, users explicitly consent to the processing of this information by Biowebspin and freely accept exclusive responsibility for doing so.

**_4.Links to other websites_**  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**_5.Our Policy Towards Minors_**

Our services are not directed to minors (persons under the age of 18). If you are under the age of 18, we ask that you not open a Biowebspin account. If you know that a minor has provided us with personal information, please contact us. If we become aware that a minor has provided us with personal information, we will take steps to remove such information and terminate the minor’s account.

**_6.Security_**

Biowebspin follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, Biowebspin cannot guarantee its absolute security. There is no guarantee that information may not be accessed, copied, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications at all times.

**_7.Important Information_**

By visiting Biowebspin you agree that the laws of France will govern this Privacy Policy and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and Biowebspin or its affiliates.

If Biowebspin decides or needs to change its Privacy Policy, it will post those changes on this privacy policy page and other places we deem appropriate. Biowebspin reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify its Privacy Policy, and any of our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, so please review this document frequently. If we make material changes to this privacy policy, we will notify you here or by means of a notice on our homepage.

**_8.Contact Us_**

For inquiries please contact:

Biowebspin,

Clément Vuarchey

123 Bis Chemin des pannetières

69126 BRINDAS

France

Biowebspin and Spinotech are tradenames of Clément Vuarchey.

© 2012 Biowebspin – Last revised: June 7, 2012.
